{
    "subject": "Ferdinand_I_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Eleanor_of_Alburquerque",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand I of Aragon is married to Eleanor of Alburquerque.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9603252410888672,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Ferdinand I of Aragon and Eleanor of Alburquerque?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9420782923698425,
            "question": "Who is Ferdinand I of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9220042824745178,
            "question": "To whom is Eleanor of Alburquerque married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.901202380657196,
            "question": "Who were the spouses of Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665682077407837,
            "question": "Name the queen who was married to King Ferdinand I of Aragon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8477321267127991,
            "question": "What is the name of the queen who was married to Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396536707878113,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand I of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8279696106910706,
            "question": "Who was the king who married Eleanor of Alburquerque?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804777026176453,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6050972938537598,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Eleanor of Alburquerque?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand I of Aragon is married to Eleanor of Alburquerque.",
            "html": "yago_29849_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand I of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_29849_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the king who married Eleanor of Alburquerque?",
            "html": "yago_29849_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Ferdinand I of Aragon's wife?",
            "html": "yago_29849_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29849_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents contain information about Eleanor of Alburquerque and her marriage to Ferdinand I of Aragon.\n* In multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_29849/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt), it is mentioned that \"Eleanor of Alburquerque became Queen consort of Aragon by her marriage to Ferdinand I of Aragon.\"\n\nTherefore, the answer to the query is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Ferdinand I of Aragon and Eleanor of Alburquerque, confirming that they were indeed married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}